Look.
Is he okay?
Is he busy recently?
I heard that
He'll fight the Physical Education Institute's students again.
For this game,
Yan has been working hard at home
to do data analysis every day.
If you really
don't want to let him down,
then hurry up,
go back and train hard.
Make sure to
do well in this game.
Listen to me,
go back now.
Fu Binyan,
we will definitely win the game,
and bring the victory
to you when you get out of the hospital.
We will work hard,
and carry Fu Binyan's spirit.
Auntie,
we'll be going now.
Take care.
Okay.
Go back now.
Goodbye, auntie.
What should we do?
We lost the game.
How can we face Fu Binyan?
We thought of so many tactics
to deal with Xie Yizhou,
but he didn't play
in the end.
I heard he's recovered.
He didn't play
on purpose.
Xie Yizhou
is like a sesame dumpling.
He looks innocent,
but he's a bad guy.
Then
in the next game,
we can only win
and can't lose, right?
Yes.
No.
I feel too bad.
I want to hit the wall.
I'm kidding.
I suddenly miss Fu Binyan so much.
At this time,
he would say something unpleasant.
We were stimulated by him.
Maybe we wouldn't feel so bad.
Yes.
If he were here
and saw us like this,
he would say
the next game is so important.
You still have time
sighing here.
You might as well hit the wall.
Especially Lin Qingyuan.
You learned it quite well.
That's right.
Fu Binyan must
know we lost.
If at this time
we fall into despair,
he will definitely be furious.
Shut up.
If it's Fu Binyan,
the result of the competition
may not be
that important to him.
What's the most important?
Our attitude towards winning or losing.
I see.
What?
You really hit the wall.
Come on, three, two, one.
How do you feel?
Pretty good.
I should
be able to get out of the hospital soon.
Whether you can get out of the hospital
depends on the doctor.
Yan,
getting sick
has caused you
some trouble, hasn't it?
I checked your watch's
heart rate monitor.
It had shown irregularities
before,
but hadn't reached the alarm threshold.
I didn't get a notification,
and you didn't tell me.
So fainting while climbing stairs
wasn't just a coincidence.
Did you push yourself too hard?
The doctor said
my heart has recovered.
I'm just like a normal person.
I can't play basketball anymore.
If I have to be careful
even when climbing stairs,
what's the difference between me and a disabled person?
So you wanted to give it a try.
If this time there's no problem with climbing stairs,
next, you'll start running,
and then playing basketball again.
right?
You're doing the right thing.
I'm with you.
I don't want you
to live in fear
because of this disease.
You want to take control again.
That's not wrong.
It's just that
we have to learn
to live with it in peace.
Live in harmony with it.
Don't try to fight it.
That's suicide.
But don't be afraid of it.
This time you got sick
was not just because
you climbed stairs.
It's because of
your staying up late, fighting, watching performances,
and all these things accumulated
to cause the result.
As long as we learn from this,
your heart will definitely
get healthier.
But, Mom,
don't you worry about me?
Of course I do.
I'm worried.
But
I want you to be happy.
So what I can do now
is to do my best
to support you,
and use the best medical resources
to back you up.
But what if
the worst-case scenario
happens?
I certainly don't hope
that the worst-case scenario will occur.
But if
it comes to that,
I hope
you can live with fewer regrets.
Mom,
what about you?
Yan,
do you know
how I feel
every time I wait
for the court decision?
As long as
I give it my all,
I won't regret it.
No matter what the result is,
I can accept it.
It's the same with you.
We have reached a consensus.
It's a deal.
Well,
I'm going to make a work call.
You continue reading.
Bin Yan,
here,
Have some water.
Your mom
told me about your situation.
I've also talked to your class advisor
and the PE teacher.
They know about it.
In the future, for things like flag raising,
calisthenics,
and PE class,
if you feel up to it,
and you want to participate, go ahead.
If you don't feel well,
you can ask for leave at any time.
We won't record your absence.
Director,
I'm not that fragile.
It's not necessary.
Bin Yan,
since you joined our school,
you've been excellent.
I've always seen you
as my capable assistant.
You've been involved in
all the activities of the school.
Violin,
competitions,
student union, and clubs.
You've done them all.
Now that I think about it,
I feel quite guilty.
Director,
this is just a normal student life.
I don't think there's any problem.
No, it's different.
I've looked into it.
Fatigue is very likely
to be
the triggering factor of your disease.
Heart problems can be serious.
We can't take any chances.
Anyway, you'll be
a priority from now on.
Director,
just listen to me.
It's really not that serious.
I'll take this call.
Hello?
Yes, yes.
Fu Binyan has returned.
From now on,
please take good care of him.
If he feels unwell,
he should come to your infirmary.
Please give him priority.
Okay.
Yes.
Thank you.
Okay.
Director
The infirmary
has known
your latest situation.
Don't worry.
There is another important thing
I want to tell you.
You are now in the student union
and the basketball club.
You have a lot of work to do.
I think
you can quit the basketball club.
I recommended you to the club
in the first place.
Now
you can quit after you have done your job.
It's reasonable.
Just listen to me.
Come on, have some water.
Fu Binyan
You lost weight.
You look pale.
You also look haggard.
Your family must be worried about you.
Coach
Don't worry.
I'm just like this.
Director Qian has told me.
I have also discussed with
Teacher Wang.
As for the Basketball Club,
if you find it hard,
you can put it off for a while.
Don't worry.
Your final score won't be affected.
It's the same old song.
Of course.
I can see that
you really love basketball.
So,
if you want to stay,
no problem.
Come by after school every day.
Just have fun.
Actually,
my regularization
is pretty much a sure thing.
Next,
I'll have more time
to devote to the club,
and Gu Chenyang can help me out.
Don't feel pressured.
You mean
I can just be a name on the roster,
and do nothing?
No problem at all.
What's the point of that?
To be a mascot?
Do I look like a mascot to you?
Coach
Thank you for your concern.
But if it's like this,
I'd rather quit the club.
Well, isn't my plan
good enough?
You are now in the student union
and the basketball club.
It's not easy.
If it's not okay, let's quit the basketball club.
If he feels unwell,
he can go to your infirmary at any time.
You should take care of him first.
As for the Basketball Club,
if you feel overwhelmed,
you can take a break.
You can go there
after school every day.
Just for fun.
Fu Binyan, you're back.
I'm looking for you.
Where are you going?
I have something to tell you.
What do you want?
I want you to teach me how to play basketball.
Last time,
I was tightly guarded by No. 8 of the other team.
I couldn't break through.
Zhou Yang said you were good at breaking through.
I've been waiting for you to get out of the hospital
to teach me how to play basketball.
I can't.
This morning, Teacher Wang came to me
and said that we should try to arrange less work
for Fu Binyan in the student union in the future.
He's afraid that Fu Binyan's body can't withstand it.
Coach Su also sent me a message.
He has a similar idea.
He wants to let him take on less burden.
What do you mean?
Don't let Fu Binyan do anything?
The teachers are worried.
Isn't that a bit too much?
Does Fu Binyan want that?
Now I know why Fu Binyan
wants us to keep it a secret.
If everyone knows
he has heart problems,
even with good intentions,
they might overreact.
Fu Binyan has heart problems?
Oh my!
When did you get here?
I've been here all the time.
It's you who didn't see me
when you came over.
What?
Fu Binyan has heart disease?
Is it that serious?
Keep your voice down.
Or do you think
why he was hospitalized?
Lin Qingyuan told me
it's the after-effects of Guo Rui beating him up.
We were so angry that we almost went to Yudong
to settle the score with them.
You two really are one who dares to guess,
and one who dares to believe.
Oh my god.
Let me catch my breath.
No wonder he
refused to join the Basketball Club.
No wonder he joined the Basketball Club,
but refused to play on the court.
No wonder you often
help him out.
I see, I see.
I see everything.
See what?
We are worried now.
In this case,
what if Fu Binyan is unhappy
and quits the club?
According to Fu Binyan's personality,
if he really
can't do anything,
he will definitely quit.
And
once he makes up his mind,
he won't change it.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
Lin Qingyuan went to find Fu Binyan.
What?
Zhou Yang, didn't you say
Fu Binyan is good at breaking through on the court?
Lin Qingyuan went to him
for one-on-one coaching.
Oh no.
Hello everyone.
You're all here.
You went to see Fu Binyan?
He taught you how to play basketball?
Stop just humming and hawing.
And then?
What's going on?
The situation is
I've learned it.
Can't teach.
Why can't you teach?
It's because I lost the game last time,
you got angry.
No.
It's just because I'm not well enough
to teach you.
And they won't let me teach you.
Why?
You just stayed in the hospital for a few days.
You're not a cripple.
What if I am?
You're fine.
You just stayed in the hospital.
How did you become like this?
So depressed.
It's not me.
It's everyone.
We've all been through it.
Zhou Yang was hospitalized,
and Gu Chenyang got injured.
They're fine now.
Look at me.
It hurts so much.
The doctor said my joint is loose
and might dislocate easily in the future.
Do you know how terrible it is?
How terrible could it be?
So bad that I can't even
eat my favorite
milk candies.
I'm afraid it'll dislocate my jaw.
Then don't eat it.
How can I do that?
I can't just because of fear,
never eat it for the rest of my life.
Don't think too much.
If it really dislocates your jaw, then we'll talk.
Try one.
If people around you
are afraid your jaw will fall off
and never let you eat candy again,
what should you do?
I can't always
listen to them, right?
I want to eat more
and be happier.
Let them know I'm fine.
You also try one.
Is it sweet?
Hurry up.
I'll teach you.
Really?
What?
Fu Binyan has heart disease?
Surprised?
Unexpected?
I've been fooled by you.
I really thought it was an accident in a fight.
Oh, no.
With such a serious illness,
I actually compared my
jaw dislocation with his.
I'm such an idiot.
No,
I think
you hit the nail on the head by accident.
What do you mean?
We just speculated that
Fu Binyan probably hates us the most
for treating him
treating him as a patient.
But you
just don't
take his illness seriously.
You ask him for help when you need it,
and complain to him when you want to.
That's exactly
what he wants.
That makes sense.
So if we treat him as if he's not sick,
and just like we always do,
he won't quit the club, right?
No.
We can't
ignore his illness.